It's news to me that it's news to you
To which degree who answers to who
We could go on and on, but in the end, who are we kidding?
My divinity is past infinity, am I...
GETTING THROUGH??
Seems our regime has plummeted south
Don't need to scream if ya ain't got a mouth
Why bite the hand that feeds when it's the only hand you're getting?
It's time you see that this great marquee is the only place you're ever gonna be
So strap on in and take it on the chin
And don't forget who's running the show!
Now look at this!
Absolute bliss!
Oh, what a shock!
Watch where you walk!
I'm the host, I run the place
Caine, that is my name!
Not enthused? Just feeling used?
Oh, what a goddamned shame!
Congratulations, all of my friends
Public relations are getting a cleanse!